=Born Again=
=Episode 3=
(Please Wait Outside the Operating Room)
Ye Shen.
(Countdown to Death)
I'm so sleepy.
Just sleep.
I'll always stay by your side.
Ye Shen.
(Two Hours Before the Wedding)
So it's an endless reset, huh?
Well, let's see then.
Whether you're torturing me,
or I'm torturing you.
Gu Xiaotang.
Are you insane?
Wedding dress.
You want me to wear the wedding dress?
What are you doing?
I'll wear it!
Wear it!
I'll wear it! Wear it!
Xiao... Xiaotang.
- Xiaotang, I...
- What are you doing here?
Is there a Ye Shen on the guest list?
What?
Who?
You? Do you know Ye Shen?
What Ye? Actually, Lu Qingyuan and I...
I see. Go ahead.
Gu Xiaotang!
Don't go!
Who is Ye Shen?
Have you been cheating on me all along?
You're disgusting.
Stop!
You'll stay till you tell me who he is!
- Gu Xiaotang
- Let go of me.
Why are you so slow this time?
Who is he? Is he that other man?
Let's talk somewhere else.
This place disgusts me.
Babe, are you okay?
Get lost!
Ye Shen, what's going on here?
Last time, I just fell asleep.
Why did the loop start again?
- Tell me.
- You did fall asleep.
But after you entered deep sleep,
your heartbeat stopped.
- What did you say?
- It seems
that death isn't the only way
to trigger the loop.
The loop also starts
when you lose consciousness.
So in this loop,
I don't even
deserve a good night's sleep.
You're right.
If we don't break this loop,
everything will be in vain.
Fine.
In that case,
I'm going off-script.
You mean...
Since this loop is tied to this wedding,
I'll just escape from it.
It will be hard.
With so many people here,
leaving quietly
is simply impossible.
Who said I'm going to leave quietly?
If I am to leave,
I'll make it spectacular.
I want everyone to see
how I shake off this pile of mud.
Still haven't found her.
Has anyone seen where she is?
- No.
- Useless!
What is Gu Xiaotang up to?
She's not bailing on us, is she?
Marrying into the Lu family
is already a huge honor,
and she dares to vanish?
I think it's a publicity stunt.
- He had to pick some nobody influencer.
- Exactly.
Looking for me?
Isn't that Gu Xiaotang?
Why isn't she in her dress?
Everyone, sorry to keep you waiting.
I just went to change my outfit.
After all,
I've been looping so many times,
so I want to try something new.
Gu Xiaotang, this is haute couture!
You're done for.
Do you all think
that I have gone crazy?
Let me tell you.
No one is clearer than me.
Because I've seen this play out
a million times.
Lu Qingyuan,
how many times have I caught
you and Xia Na cheating?
I can't even count anymore.
Director Li,
no matter how many times we restart,
you always use the same tricks on me.
Aren't you tired of it?
And you too, Mrs. Lu.
The way you lie on the operating table,
waiting to harvest my kidney,
doesn't look like a noble lady at all.
Really?
What nonsense are you talking about?
How could you say Lu Qingyuan and I
have been caught by you so many times?
Do you have any proof?
If you keep talking nonsense,
I'll sue you for slander.
How did I use tricks on you?
I'm helping you.
No one's admitting it, huh?
Ye Shen!
Who's he?
Who is this man?
It's you,
the thug who just beat me up.
You dare to come here?
Do you want to die?
You don't dare to admit your affair.
I'll admit it. That's right.
Ye Shen is my lover.
Isn't he attractive?
- Lover?
Since you already had someone else,
why did you agree
to marry into the Lu family?
You humiliate the Lu family like this.
What do you really want?
You've got it wrong, Mrs. Lu.
I want the Lu family.
Lu Qingyuan,
you cheated on me,
and still play the loving couple.
You love to act so much.
I'll act with you then.
I
will marry you today anyway.
Not only will I be Mrs. Lu,
I'm going to spend your money,
live off your fortune,
and use your wealth
to keep my lover.
I'll put the greenest cuckold's crown
right on your head.
You...
What's that look?
One rule for you,
another for us?
And you.
Aren't you in poor health?
Don't worry.
I will definitely
take very good care of you.
I'll make sure
that every day from now on,
you'll wish you were dead,
but I won't let you.
Emcee!
The wedding continues.
Don't listen to her.
Gu Xiaotang,
you just drag some random guy
and say he's your man?
Do you think we're all idiots?
Don't believe her, everyone.
She's just doing this for publicity.
Seeing the Lu family's decline,
you found a pretty boy
to put on a show of rebelling for love,
just to extend
your influencer career, right?
Miss Gu,
can you prove your relationship?
Mr. Ye, how did you two meet?
Are they just doing this for publicity?
We've been best friends
for so many years.
How could I not know
if you have a boyfriend?
I guess
you don't even know
where he lives, right?
This is fraud.
I'm calling the police.
You're done for.
Gu Xiaotang.
You just brought some random man here,
trying to blackmail the Lu family.
I'll sue you for marriage fraud.
♪The face deep in the heart♪
♪Suddenly clear and hazy♪
♪Across time and space, eyes meet again♪
♪Deeply trapped in the vortex♪
♪Searching for familiar outlines♪
♪Persistently guarding,
endlessly cycling♪
♪Even for just a second♪
♪If raindrops flow backward
into the sky♪
♪And sunlight reverses♪
♪As the sun rises and sets,
we reunite with yesterday♪
♪I'll build a dream with you♪
♪Upon the ruins, spring breeze arrives♪
♪Even if there's no end,
I won't regret the start♪
♪Eternity like a day, rushing to you♪
♪You don't need to recognize my eyes♪
♪Following the tracks
of the days that were♪
♪A day like a lifetime, rushing to you♪
♪You don't need to remember my name♪
♪I'll be the dawn you haven't seen♪